http://www.whiteface.com/privacy-policy

View Report
Search for:
Belleayre
Welcome to ORDA. We understand that privacy online is important to users of our Site, especially when conducting business. This statement governs our privacy policies with respect to those users of the Site (“Visitors”). “Personally Identifiable Information” Refers to any information that identifies or can be used to identify, contact, or locate the person to whom such information pertains, including, but not limited to, name, address, phone number, fax number, and email. Personally Identifiable Information does not include information that is collected anonymously (that is, without identification of the individual user) or demographic information not connected to an identified individual.
WHAT PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION IS COLLECTED?
We may collect basic user profile information from all of our Visitors. We collect the following additional information from our Visitors: the names, addresses, phone numbers and email addresses of Visitors, the nature and size of the business, and the nature and size of the advertising inventory that the Visitors intends to purchase or sell.
WHAT ORGANIZATIONS ARE COLLECTING THE INFORMATION?
In addition to our direct collection of information, our third party service vendors (such as credit card companies, clearinghouses and banks) who may provide such services as credit, insurance, and escrow services may collect this information from our Visitors. We do not control how these third parties use such information, but we do ask them to disclose how they use personal information provided to them from Visitors. Some of these third parties may be intermediaries that act solely as links in the distribution chain, and do not store, retain, or use the information given to them.
HOW DOES THE SITE USE PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION?
We use Personally Identifiable Information to customize the Site, to make appropriate service offerings, and to fulfill buying and selling requests on the Site. We may email Visitors about research or purchase and selling opportunities on the Site or information related to the subject matter of the Site. We may also use Personally Identifiable Information to contact Visitors in response to specific inquiries, or to provide requested information.
WITH WHOM MAY THE INFORMATION MAY BE SHARED?
We may share aggregated information about our Visitors, including the demographics of our Visitors, with our affiliated agencies and third party vendors. We also offer the opportunity to “opt out” of receiving information or being contacted by us or by any agency acting on our behalf.
HOW IS PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION STORED?
Personally Identifiable Information collected by ORDA is securely stored and is not accessible to third parties or employees of ORDA except for use as indicated above.
WHAT CHOICES ARE AVAILABLE TO VISITORS REGARDING COLLECTION, USE AND DISTRIBUTION OF THE INFORMATION?
Visitors may opt out of receiving unsolicited information from or being contacted by us and/or our vendors and affiliated agencies by responding to emails as instructed, or by contacting us at:
ORDA
info@orda.org
ARE COOKIES USED ON THE SITE?
Cookies are used for a variety of reasons. We use Cookies to obtain information about the preferences of our Visitors and the services they select. We also use Cookies for security purposes to protect our Visitors.
WHAT PARTNERS OR SERVICE PROVIDERS HAVE ACCESS TO PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION FROM VISITORS ON THE SITE?
ORDA has entered into and will continue to enter into partnerships and other affiliations with a number of vendors. Such vendors may have access to certain Personally Identifiable Information on a need to know basis for evaluating Visitors for service eligibility. Our privacy policy does not cover their collection or use of this information. Disclosure of Personally Identifiable Information to comply with law. We will disclose Personally Identifiable Information in order to comply with a court order or subpoena or a request from a law enforcement agency to release information. We will also disclose Personally Identifiable Information when reasonably necessary to protect the safety of our Visitors.
HOW DOES THE SITE KEEP PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION SECURE?
All of our employees are familiar with our security policy and practices. The Personally Identifiable Information of our Visitors is only accessible to a limited number of qualified employees who are given a password in order to gain access to the information. We audit our security systems and processes on a regular basis. Sensitive information is protected by encryption protocols to protect information sent over the Internet. While we take commercially reasonable measures to maintain a secure site, electronic communications and databases are subject to errors, tampering and break-ins, and we cannot guarantee or warrant that such events will not take place and we will not be liable to Visitors for any such occurrences.
HOW CAN VISITORS CORRECT ANY INACCURACIES IN PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION?
Visitors may contact us to update Personally Identifiable Information about them or to correct any inaccuracies by emailing us at info@orda.org
CAN A VISITOR DELETE OR DEACTIVATE PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION COLLECTED BY THE SITE?
We provide Visitors with a mechanism to delete/deactivate Personally Identifiable Information from the Site’s database by contacting us at info@orda.org. However, because of backups and records of deletions, it may be impossible to delete a Visitor’s entry without retaining some residual information. An individual who requests to have Personally Identifiable Information deactivated will have this information functionally deleted, and we will not sell, transfer, or use Personally Identifiable Information relating to that individual in any way moving forward.
WHAT HAPPENS IF THE PRIVACY POLICY CHANGES?
We will let our Visitors know about changes to our privacy policy by posting such changes on the Site. However, if we are changing our privacy policy in a manner that might cause disclosure of Personally Identifiable Information that a Visitor has previously requested not be disclosed, we will contact such Visitor to prevent such disclosure.
FORM SUBMISSIONS
By submitting forms on this website, you accept the ORDA privacy policy.
LINKS
This web site contains links to other web sites. Please note that when you click on one of these links, you are moving to another web site. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of these linked sites as their privacy policies may differ from ours.
© 2012 ORDA All rights reserved.
Unauthorized duplication or publication of any materials from this Site is expressly prohibited.
Cookies are used for measurement, ads, and optimization. By continuing to use our site you agree to our privacy policy. ACCEPTPrivacy & Cookies Policy
Close
Privacy Overview
This website uses cookies to improve your experience while you navigate through the website. Out of these cookies, the cookies that are categorized as necessary are stored on your browser as they are essential for the working of basic functionalities of the website. We also use third-party cookies that help us analyze and understand how you use this website. These cookies will be stored in your browser only with your consent. You also have the option to opt-out of these cookies. But opting out of some of these cookies may have an effect on your browsing experience.
Necessary
Necessary
Always Enabled
Necessary cookies are absolutely essential for the website to function properly. This category only includes cookies that ensures basic functionalities and security features of the website. These cookies do not store any personal information.
Non-necessary
Non-necessary
Any cookies that may not be particularly necessary for the website to function and is used specifically to collect user personal data via analytics, ads, other embedded contents are termed as non-necessary cookies. It is mandatory to procure user consent prior to running these cookies on your website.
